Spence, Bill and Andy; Papers apap400
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1960-2022; 2; 3.45 cubic ft.
  - "Mellow with Ale from the Horn," John Roberts and Tony Barrand, 1975 (Lp 34)
  - Monthly Planning Guide, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Natural Selections," Mark Graham, 1987 (Lp 35)
  - New York State Presenters Network Dinner Meeting, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - North American Folk Music and Dance Alliance, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - North American Folk Music and Dance Alliance, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - North American Folk Music and Dance Alliance, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - North American Folk Music and Dance Alliance, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - North American Folk Music and Dance Alliance, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - North American Folk Music and Dance Alliance, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - North American Folk Music and Dance Alliance, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - North American Folk Music and Dance Alliance, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - North American Folk Music and Dance Alliance, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - North American Folk Music and Dance Alliance, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - "Nowell Sing We Clear Vol. 3," John Roberts, Tony Barrand, Fred Breunig, and Steve Woodruff, 1985 (Lp 36)
  - "Oh! That Low Bridge!: Songs of the Erie Canal," George Ward, 1982 (Lp 37)
  - "The Old Road," Solomon's Seal, 1984 (Lp 38)
  - "Old Songs, Old Friends," Louis Killen, 1978 (Lp 39)
  - "The Other Side of my Fiddle," Bob Beers, Undated (Lp 40)
  - "A Pageant of Mid-Winter Carols," Nowell Sing We Clear, 1977 (Lp 41)
  - "A Pageant of Mid-Winter Carols, The Second Nowell," Nowell Sing We Clear, Vol. 2, 1981 (Lp 42)
  - Personal Planner, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Richard and Lee Wilkie, 1962; 1967-1973; Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "Saturday Night in the Provinces," Fennig's All-Star String Band, 1975 (Lp 43)
  - "Settle Down," Cindy Mangsen, 1988 (Lp 44)
  - "Singer of Old Songs," Michael Cooney, 1976 (Lp 45)
  - "Still Cooney After All These Years," Michael Cooney, 1979 (Lp 46)
  - "Swinging on a Gate," Dudley Laufman and the Canterbury Orchestra, 1974 (Lp 47)
  - "Traditional Music of Ireland: A Point of Departure," How To Change a Flat Tire, 1977 (Lp 48)
  - "Traditional Music of Ireland and Shetland," How To Change a Flat Tire, 1978 (Lp 49)
  - "Traditional Tunes: English Concertina and Northumbrian Small Pipes," Alistair Anderson, 1976 (Lp 50)
  - "The Visitors," Directed by Andy Spence, 2007-2010 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - "The VISITORS: the History, Music and Songs of the Adirondacks", 2008 (Cd 10)
  - "The VISITORS - LIVE at the GE Theatre," November 7, 2009 (Cd 11)
  - "Walkie in the Parlor (Songs with Ancient Psaltery) With Fiddler Beers and Evelyne", Undated (Cd 12)
  - "To Welcome in the Spring," John Roberts, Tony Barrand, Fred Breunig, and Steve Woodruff, 1980 (Lp 51)
  - "Where Have All the Flowers Gone" by Pete Seeger, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin', 1967-2021; 3; 1.0 cubic ft.
  Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' (PSG) is a Capital District traditional folk music and dance organization formed in 1966 by Bill and Andy Spence, along with Bill Little, Richard and Lee Wilkie, Bob and Evelyne Beers, Sterling Pierce, Rev. James Bordon, Lucille Tasker, Barbara Smith, and Irv Rosenberg. The not-for-profit organization encourages participatory events that get the family involved in folk music singing and playing. PSG was involved with the planning of the Beers family's Fox Hollow Festival during its run. Each year, PSG holds a Memorial Day weekend folk music event called Gottagetgon, which is referenced in these records. This series contains posters, news clippings, photographs, meeting minutes, flyers, business correspondence, and more from Andy's time with PSG in the
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (1 of 3), 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (2 of 3), 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (3 of 3), 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Board Meeting Minutes, 1967-1974; 1976; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (1 of 3), 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (2 of 3), 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (3 of 3), 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Directories, 1983; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (1 of 2), 1985-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (2 of 2), 1985-1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (1 of 2), 2000-2007 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (2 of 2), 2000-2007 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (1 of 2), 2008-2021 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Pickin' and Singin' Gatherin' Binder (2 of 2), 2008-2021 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Old Songs Administration, 1993-2014; 4; 3.03 cubic ft.
  Founded in 1977 by Bill and Andy Spence, Old Songs, Inc. is a not-for-profit, educational corporation that sponsors and hosts classes, workshops, performances, and more to promote traditional folk music and dance. This series focuses on the administrative side of the organization. Andy Spence served as executive director of Old Songs, Inc. until 2018 when she became executive director emeritus. She also served on the board in varying positions from the 1990s to the 2010s. Board of Director binders containing fiscal reports, agreements, business correspondence, meeting minutes, emails, planning documents, flyers, agendas, event information, newsletters, and more are included in this series.
  - 1996-1997 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 1993-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1996-1997 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 1993-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1998-1999 Board of Directors Binder, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1995-1996 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1995-1996 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2001-2002 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 1995-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2001-2002 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 1995-2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dutch Barn Concerts Poster, 1996 Board of Directors Binder (Oversize 3, Folder 3)
  - 1997-1998 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1997-1998 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1999-2000 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1999-2000 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 1997-2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 2000-2001 Board of Directors Binder (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - March 2002 - February 2003 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - March 2002 - February 2003 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors Concert Notebook, 2001-2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - March 2003 - February 2004 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - March 2003 - February 2004 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - March 2004 - February 2005 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - March 2004 - February 2005 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - March 2005 - February 2006 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - March 2005 - February 2006 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 3), 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - March 2005 - February 2006 Board of Directors Binder (3 of 3), 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - March 2006 - February 2007 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - March 2006 - February 2007 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - March 2007 - February 2008 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - March 2007 - February 2008 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - March 2008 - February 2009 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2007-2009 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - March 2008 - February 2009 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 2007-2009 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - March 2009 - February 2010 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - March 2009 - February 2010 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - March 2013 - February 2014 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2008; 2012-2014 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - March 2013 - February 2014 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 2008; 2012-2014 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - March 2010 - February 2011 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2009-2012 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - March 2010 - February 2011 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 2009-2012 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - March 2011 - February 2012 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2009-2012 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - March 2011 - February 2012 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 2009-2012 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, March 2010 - February 2011 Board of Directors Binder, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors Planner, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - March 2012 - February 2013 Board of Directors Binder (1 of 2), 2011-2017 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - March 2012 - February 2013 Board of Directors Binder (2 of 2), 2011-2017 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors Planner, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors Applications, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Old Songs Activities, 1977-2022; 5; 8.78 cubic ft.
  Founded in 1977 by Bill and Andy Spence, Old Songs, Inc. is a not-for-profit, educational corporation that sponsors and hosts classes, workshops, performances, and more to promote traditional folk music and dance. Bill was a performer for Old Songs events and part of the folk group Fennig's All-Star Band on the hammered dulcimer. Andy Spence was executive director of the organization until 2018, when she became executive director emeritus, and served on the Board of Directors from the 1990s to 2017. This series consists of notebooks, flyers, correspondence, tickets, newsletters, records, magazines, posters, and more from activities and events occurring during Andy's time with the organization.
  The biggest event held by Old Songs, Inc. was and still is the annual Old Songs Festival each June. The Old Songs Festival is a festival of folk, traditional, Celtic and world music and dance, sponsored and organized by Old Songs, Inc., bringing in musicians from around the globe. A large portion of this series is photographs and negatives from the annual festival and other performances. This festival was first held in Guilderland, N.Y. in 1981, before moving permanently to the fairgrounds in Altamont, New York the following year. Each June, thousands of folk music enthusiasts travel to the festival, often camping out, to enjoy an entire weekend of folk performances, classes, participatory workshops, dancing, crafts, games, vendors, children's activities, and food. Andy's festival planning notebooks (detailing the festival programs, guests, lodging, grounds, accommodations, etc.) are available in this series. In 1994, Old Songs embarked on a plan to sponsor the construction of an 18th century style Dutch barn on the Altamont fairgrounds to become the Center for Traditional Arts and Agriculture, with maps, site plans, and information on the old Dutch barn included here. The series contains A/V materials, including CDs, cassettes, VHS tapes, audio reels, DATs and more from the Old Songs Festivals.
  Records of other activities held by Old Songs, Inc., which include band performances, musicals, instrumental classes, and dance workshops year-round, also are available in this series. Annual reports appear in this series as they list all festivals, concerts, dances, classes, camps, programs, and rentals, and not just expenses and income.
  - Old Songs Concert Part 3, 1977 September (Cassette 1)
  - Oct '77 Concert Old Songs, 1977 October (Cassette 2)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photographs Fiddle Class, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Old Songs Concert, Peter Belamy, 1979 September 17 (Cassette 3)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Old Songs Poster, 1979 (Oversize 3, Folder 4)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Old Songs Posters, 1981 (Oversize 3, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Festival and Planning, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence to Andy and Bill With Festival Photos, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Old Songs Festival Posters, 1982 (Oversize 3, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Festival and Performers, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Old Songs Sampler, 1983 January (Cassette 4)
  - Negatives, Old Songs Festival by Emily Friedman, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Old Songs Festival Poster, 1983 (Oversize 2, Folder 2)
  - Old Songs Slides used for Calendar, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Old Songs Festival Feature- Sunday Night Folk Festival, WHUS Storrs, CT, 1984 June 24 (Cassette 5)
  - Contact Sheets, Staff Photos by Jean Redpath, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Negatives, Old Songs Festival by Emily Friedman, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Old Songs St. Patrick's Day Poster, 1984 (Oversize 2, Folder 3)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Performance and Festival, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Slides, Old Songs Festival Crew, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Slides, Old Songs Performance, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1986 Festival Saturday 5 pm (Cassette 6)
  - 1986 Festival Saturday Eve (Cassette 7)
  - Old Songs 30 Second PSA "Big John McNeal", 1986 (Umatic 1)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Old Songs Event Posters, 1986 (Oversize 2, Folder 4)
  - Old Songs Festival 1986 "Big John McNeal" (1-inch type c 1)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 1, 1986 (Cassette 8)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 2, 1986 (Cassette 9)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 3, 1986 (Cassette 10)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 4, 1986 (Cassette 11)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 5, 1986 (Cassette 12)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 6, 1986 (Cassette 13)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 7, 1986 (Cassette 14)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 8, 1986 (Cassette 15)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Festival, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Negatives, Photographs, and Slides, Old Songs Festival and Performance, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Old Songs 30 Second PSA "Big John McNeal", 1987 (Umatic 2)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Old Songs Festival Poster, 1987 (Oversize 2, Folder 5)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 1, 1987 (Cassette 16)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 2, 1987 (Cassette 17)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 3, 1987 (Cassette 18)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 4, 1987 (Cassette 19)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 5, 1987 (Cassette 20)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 6, 1987 (Cassette 21)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 7, 1987 (Cassette 22)
  - Negatives and Photographs, Old Songs Activities, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Old Songs Festival Poster, 1988 (Oversize 2, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, Old Songs, 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Old Songs Festival: Friday (Tape 1), 1989 June 23 (Cassette 23)
  - Old Songs Festival: Friday (Tape 2), 1989 June 23 (Cassette 24)
  - Old Songs Festival: Friday (Tape 3), 1989 June 23 (Cassette 25)
  - Old Songs Festival: Saturday, 1989 June 24 (Cassette 26)
  - Old Songs Festival: Saturday (Tape 2), 1989 June 24 (Cassette 27)
  - Old Song Festival: Saturday (Tape 5), 1989 June 24 (Cassette 28)
  - Old Song Festival: Saturday (Tape 6), 1989 June 24 (Cassette 29)
  - Old Songs Festival: Sunday (Tape 1), 1989 June 25 (Cassette 30)
  - Old Songs Festival: Sunday (Tape 2), 1989 June 25 (Cassette 31)
  - Old Songs Festival: Sunday (Tape 3), 1989 June 25 (Cassette 32)
  - Contact Sheets and Correspondence with Craig Harris, Old Songs Festival, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Negatives and Photographs, Old Songs Festival, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Old Songs Festival Promo, Sampler for Air Play Only, 1989 (Cassette 33)
  - Old Songs: First Cut, Public Radio Network, Recorded Live Outdoors, Tape 1, 1989 (Cassette 34)
  - Old Songs: First Cut, Public Radio Network, Recorded Live Outdoors, Tape 2, 1989 (Cassette 35)
  - Old Songs Posters, 1989 (Oversize 2, Folder 7)
  - Tape Information, Old Songs Festival, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 1, 1990 June 22 (Cassette 36)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 2, 1990 June 22 (Cassette 37)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 3, 1990 June 22 (Cassette 38)
  - Old Songs Tape 1, 1990 June 22 (Digital audio tape 1)
  - Old Songs Tape 1A, 1990 June 22 (Digital audio tape 2)
  - Old Songs Tape 2, 1990 June 22 (Digital audio tape 3)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 4, 1990 June 23 (Cassette 39)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 5, 1990 June 23 (Cassette 40)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 6, 1990 June 23 (Cassette 41)
  - Old Songs Tape 3, 1990 June 23 (Digital audio tape 4)
  - Old Songs Tape 4, 1990 June 23 (Digital audio tape 5)
  - Old Songs Tape 5, 1990 June 23 (Digital audio tape 6)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 7, 1990 June 24 (Cassette 42)
  - Old Songs Festival, Tape 8, 1990 June 24 (Cassette 43)
  - Old Songs Tape 6, 1990 June 24 (Digital audio tape 7)
  - Old Songs Tape 7, 1990 June 24 (Digital audio tape 8)
  - Arts, Entertainment Map and Guide, 1990 June (Oversize 2, Folder 8)
  - Negatives and Photographs, Old Songs Activities, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Old Songs Poster, 1990 (Oversize 2, Folder 9)
  - Pins, Old Songs Festival, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Old Songs Clippings, 1990-1991 (Oversize 3, Folder 7)
  - Negative and Photographs, Old Songs Festival Crew, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Slides, Old Songs Festival, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Wooden Nickel, Old Songs Festival, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Negatives, Old Songs Activities, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Old Songs Festival Commercial, 1992 (Cassette 44)
  - 1992 Census of Service Industries, Old Songs Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 1993 Old Songs Festival Video by Bill Spence (Vhs 1)
  - Data Recording Notes, Old Songs Festival, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Lucky Wooden Nickel, Old Songs Festival, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Negatives and Photographs, Old Songs Festival, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - "Old Songs Festival of Traditional Music and Dance, 1990, The Tenth Anniversary", 1993 (Cd 13)
  - Old Songs Festival Tape 1, 1993 (Digital audio tape 9)
  - Old Songs Festival Tape 2, 1993 (Digital audio tape 10)
  - Old Songs Festival Tape 3, 1993 (Digital audio tape 11)
  - Old Songs Festival Tape 5, 1993 (Digital audio tape 12)
  - Old Songs Festival Tape 6, 1993 (Digital audio tape 13)
  - Old Songs Festival Tape 7, 1993 (Digital audio tape 14)
  - Old Songs Festival Tape 8, 1993 (Digital audio tape 15)
  - Old Songs Festival Tape 9, 1993 (Digital audio tape 16)
  - Dutch Barn Construction, 1993-1995; Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1993 Old Songs Festival VHS Details, 1994 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Dutch Barn Elevations, 1994 April 15 (Map-tube 1)
  - Dutch Barn Foundation and Floor Plan, 1994 April 15 (Map-tube 1)
  - Dutch Barn Wall Sections and Foundation Details, 1994 April 15 (Map-tube 1)
  - Dutch Barn Site Plan, 1994 May 30 (Map-tube 1)
  - Old Songs Sacred Harp Workshop, 1994 June 25 (Cassette 45)
  - Dutch Barns of New York, An Introduction by Vincent J. Schaefer, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Negatives and Photographs, Old Songs Festival, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Friday Tape 1, 1994 (Digital audio tape 17)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Friday Tape 2, 1994 (Digital audio tape 18)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Harp 1, 1994 (Digital audio tape 19)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Harp 2, 1994 (Digital audio tape 20)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Tape 3, 1994 (Digital audio tape 21)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Tape 4, 1994 (Digital audio tape 22)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Tape 5, 1994 (Digital audio tape 23)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Tape 6, 1994 (Digital audio tape 24)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Tape 7, 1994 (Digital audio tape 25)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Tape 8, 1994 (Digital audio tape 26)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Tape 9, 1994 (Digital audio tape 27)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Tape 10, 1994 (Digital audio tape 28)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Tape 11, 1994 (Digital audio tape 29)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Tape 12, 1994 (Digital audio tape 30)
  - Old Songs Festival '94 Tape 13, 1994 (Digital audio tape 31)
  - Old Songs Festival Notebook, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Old Songs, Inc. "Festival of Traditional Music & Dance," WEQX Productions, 1994 (Cassette 46)
  - Photographs, 1994 Old Songs Festival Taken by Max Tiller (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Clippings, Old Songs, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Sacred Harp '94 Old Songs, 1995 January 18 (Digital audio tape 32)
  - Chorus Songs at Old Songs, 1995 June 24 (Cassette 47)
  - Old Songs Acapella Singing (1 of 2), 1995 June 24 (Cassette 48)
  - Old Songs Acapella Singing (2 of 2), 1995 June 24 (Cassette 49)
  - Old Songs Lap Dulcimer, 1995 June 24 (Cassette 50)
  - Old Songs Sacred Harp, 1995 June 24 (Cassette 51)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Benefit for Center, 1995 November (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Altamont Fair Festival of Lights Poster, 1995 (Oversize 3, Folder 8)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Old Songs Festival Wooden Nickel, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Barn Frame, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Festival, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Weddings at the Old's Songs Dutch Barn, 1995; 1998 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Photographs, Nowell Sing We Clear, 1996 December 14 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Photograph, Winners of the '96 Quilt, 1996 September (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Negatives and Photographs, Old Songs Festival, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Old Songs Festival Gloucester Old Spot Pig Sheet Music Bag, 1996 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Old Songs Inc. Subscribers Memo Book, March, 1996-2002 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Dutch Barn Site Plan Phase #2, 1997 February (Map-tube 1)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Old Songs Twenty Year Pin, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - 1997 Economic Census, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - DBA Account, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 1998 Contracts, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Clippings, Patrick Ball, 1998 (Oversize 2, Folder 10)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 19th Annual Old Songs Festival Original #1, Recorded by Robert Millman, Altamont Fairgrounds, 1999 June 26 (Beta 1)
  - Old Songs Festival VHS Window Dub #1, 1999 June 26 (Vhs 2)
  - 19th Annual Old Songs Festival Original #2, Recorded by Robert Millman, Altamont Fairgrounds, 1999 June 26-1999 June 27 (Beta 2)
  - Old Songs Festival VHS Window Dub #2, 1999 June 26-1999 June 27 (Vhs 3)
  - Photographs, Old Songs Samplers, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Negatives and Photographs, Old Songs Festival Staff and Crew, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Old Songs Activities, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Old Songs Festival Pin, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Old Songs Inc. 1998 Fiscal Year Annual Report (March 1, 1998-February 28, 1999), ca. 1999 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - 2000 Monthly Planning Guide Old Songs Calendar, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - "Live from the Dutch Barn, Old Songs Festival, 20th Anniversary Commemorative Recording", 2000 (Cd 14)
  - Old Songs Activities, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 1)